Hello everyone, this is Anda Yamamoto from Equal Love!
It's the first time for me to introduce myself!
I'm Geimi Ota.
Yay!
Well, what a day!
It's a thank you party for all the hard work you've done on that stage.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And two more.
thanks for looking.
I've seen it.
As much as you want today.
I did.
Enjoyed it.
Yay!
I'm going to eat a lot!
What's more...
Look at this!
Beer.
Miri, you have
Shochu and cranberry juice.
Ankoro and Mochiko...
What a surprise for me!
Dancing!
No pressure
I'm glad to hear it.
Shall I propose a toast?
Yes!
Well, I guess I'll be the toast girl.
I'll do it.
Go ahead.
Yes, for now.
I'd like to thank you all for your hard work on my stage.
I'd also like to thank you all for your hard work on the stage.
Cheers!
Great!
Delicious!
I know this isn't the third time we've done a sake event here on the AJ channel, you know, like the "People 3" or the "Morning Stabber 3" or something, but you've always wanted to do one, right?
I've always wanted to say that I wanted to do it at my cousin's place, because it's a collaboration with three sisters.
I'm so glad you're here!
Thank you very much.
bees aho
What shall we do?
Let's cook up some meat.
I'll let you have the salad and we'll call it a night.
Salad.
Thank you very much.
What's this?
Do we need plates?
Cheese.
Here you go.
Salad.
Thank you.
This is awesome.
They can bake bread and make sandwiches.
That's great.
Mashed potatoes look delicious.
Bread, everybody!
Bread.
I'm going to bake bread!
I'm baking!
Scary!
I've never done this before.
Are you okay? Hey, sis.
I can do it.
Here we go.
Can you do it?
Wow!
Open!
Wow.
Where am I gonna put this? Around here?
Yeah, it's okay, right?
Is it right?Am I right?
Over here!
This way?
Is it right?
Let's just put it down.
You want some?
Ah! What? For the pretty lady!
What? It's for beautiful women.
Beauty... Oh, I got it already.
It's for a pretty girl.
What? Wait!
I love the moon!
There? It's not meat.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
They're grilling.
Okay, you want some meat?
Let's get some meat.
But we're early.
It's early.
Oh, that looks good.
It is.
Oh! Looks delicious.
I'm so happy.
A cute girl baked it for me.
I've never been so happy.
Make it delicious! Make it white and kimono.
I hope it's delicious. But it's a good thing the weather's nice.
It's so nice to work under blue skies.
It's late in the evening.
A little crispy, but still a little firm
Put it in!
Put it in, put it in, put it in!
Let it in! Let it in!
Come here.
The three of us can fish here.
It's short.
Ta-da!
Corona's on right now.
Did you see it?
You saw it?
It started on the 14th, right?
Yeah, it was early.
I didn't see it until the next day.
Was it funny?
Yeah, it was fast.
It was fun.
People aren't making a fuss? All the people in the world?
Are you excited?
It's out today!
I heard that.
Mm-hmm.
It's coming out today!
Today!
Mmm-hmm.
That was fun.
Okay, okay.
It wasn't.
Bread
Bread is done!
Bread.
Let's cook some meat.
Sanna, would you like to cook?
Yes, I do.
Electron.
Keyboard?
Right hand up, left hand down.
Like a piano?
Let's do it there.
Well, if it burns, it's the same.
I don't know, I've been listening to a lot of your collaborators during the show.
What did you listen to the most?
When we were 7 nerds, it was spring, a little before spring, so I was listening to Trigger.
And now, now, when I was listening to Pearny...
I was listening to Liesel and Coupling.
I was listening to the songs on the album.
When you're a gyaru, do you listen to gyaru-ish songs?
Oh, you mean like that?
Yeah, and Weekend Strawberry and stuff like that.And Weekend Strawberries.
Oh, you're not gonna close this?
Close it?
That's a meatball, I'm gonna put it all in.
Where is it? Here?
Right there.
Wait, wait, wait.
I was with you today.
I'm with you. I'm with all of you.
You've grown, and so has Anna.
I didn't mean Anna too.
It's like a big...
Fresh corn.
It smells so good.
Is this okay?
It's gonna fly.
Do you want to put the vegetables in, too?
You want to close the lid?
Yeah. - Okay.
She's a beauty.
Where is it?
There? You're gonna put it there?
Beauty's good.
I like beautiful women.
Looks good.
I've always wanted to barbecue something like that.
That's what I've always wanted to barbecue.
Let's put it on top. It's good, it's good, it's good.
Close the lid and make sure it doesn't burn while we're talking.
That's it.
See you later.
How long is the meat?
It's not too tough, is it?
It was thick.
Have the three of you ever been out to dinner?
No, not the three of us.
I mean, there were a few of them here.
Not at your house, like the four of us?
We've been there before.
I remember.
It's hard to say.
I think we've been hanging out since lunch.
I don't remember that.
You had a sleepover.
You woke up during the day and hung around.
Maybe twice.
That might have happened.
Yes, we did.
After work, me and Minna got off work.
I joined Maika and Sana.
They were so excited.
They were drinking.
They had been drinking.
They greeted me with high spirits.
Maika made hamburgers.
Really?
That's not a hoo.
We were together.
Maika made hamburgers at my request.
She made a lot of hamburgers, and we ate a lot.
Like this.
It's been a while since I've had dinner with the members.
It's nice, sisters.
Sisters!
Pom!
Thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you.
Pong.
Aah!
It's okay, it's okay.
Who was that? You just said that.
Oh, my God.
Sana, you've been busy.
Yeah, I've been busy.
You must have been very busy.
I was very busy.
You started rehearsing right after the first play?
Yeah.
Two days after we finished the first seven, we started rehearsals for the new gal.
We started rehearsals for a new show.The rehearsals for the play have started.
And before the first one...
I had a lot of work to do before the first one, didn't I?
Budokan.
The Budokan.
The day of the Budokan and the stage...
And you two were on the same stage.
I was doing this amazing Budokan.
I was doing it the next day.
Bang bang!
Oh, man.
In the meantime, you have to practice for the Budokan.
you have to memorize your lines, right?
But you know what?
I had a moment of clarity.
The story-telling session...
You know?
And you know how they have their own rooms?
And everyone...
Baseball was in full swing.
Or...
And each one of us was taking it easy.
Sana, I was wondering what you're doing.
I wondered how she was doing.
I thought I'd go over to Sanna's.
And when I peeked in, she was reading her script.
So I thought...
I thought I'd leave her alone.
I thought, "That's great.
The world was really excited about the WBC.
I was at a talk with a fan.
You told me you saw a baseball game.
I'm really sorry.
I'm just following the conversation.
It was really fun.
Thank you so much for your hard work.
I'd also like to do a play with all the members.
It's still something I watch... us.
Of course we do.
We love you so much!
We should all see it together.
When I went with Akiho...
We all saw it together.
We saw it.
High class
Big high class
You cried, right?
We were crying all the time.
We were crying because we thought it was a work of art.
But to be honest...
I wasn't very good at it at first.
But... when we did it...
Four or five years ago?
After I did it, I thought it was fun.
I know.
It was hard then.
Are you sure your glasses aren't crooked?
They're crooked.
Why would they be crooked?
I've been complaining about it all week.
I'd say it's more like a tiny little word than a tiny little part of a pretty face, but if they're crooked, well, they're crooked.
Well, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now.
I'm sure you'll be fine...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
I want to check it out!
ft 13
manual
horizon me
Hey einz
good bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
ok theme park
I don't care what it is, because there was no script today, and yes, the script was really, really flimsy.
I mean, the script was really, really flimsy, and the toast section, it just said, "Here's to the best of your best.
I was told that I was going to be in the meeting, and I brought that thing, and they said, "I'll do it, and then you'll do it again.
I'll do it without meeting with them.
Higo from Acho Club was in the show, and he was so gorgeous that he said he'd do most of Higo's gags, even though we did "Hot" last week
me He said he laughed so hard when he did "azatsu oden" during the last curtain call!I was laughing so hard because they did "azatsu-oden" at the last curtain call!
He said he laughed so hard because they did "Azatsu Oden" at the curtain call at the end.
I like the way he plays the role of a hanged man so much.
What's that? What? What? What? What are you laughing at?
Two shows ago, you did a show called "The Last Bunny Show.
The Last Bunny Show? Yeah, you came to see me.
I went to see the show, and I got a message from the mummy... with a picture of you.
A selfie of me on the train, crying my eyes out.
I was so embarrassed, but I was really moved.
She sent me a picture of herself crying, like she was really moved.
I thought it was funny. It's so cute. Remember? I remember. She was crying so hard.
You're so squeamish. I get squeamish when I talk about that play.
What? What? I just think you're doing a great job.
I know, I know. But I totally understand. You know how Hana recently did a reading by herself?
I cried when I saw that too. I know. I cried from the very first sentence.
That was quick, wasn't it? What's the difference?
I'm not drunk.
We really love the members too much.
I understand. That's why I like Rosemuse.
They're a good group. They're a good group. They're really doing their best.
They're really working hard. They've got a showroom here. They've got us eating our chi.
I'm so glad she specializes in this.
That music video made me so happy. How was it? How was it?
Who did you tell the most? Your mom?
Maybe the fans? This is a song that the fans can sing along with.
It's really different from my solo songs, so I guess it's the fans.
I didn't expect to see my dad on the stage. He's a real dad.
And your friends were amazing, too, because they got to show their faces.
The making of the movie is really bad. I'm editing it right now.
That's right! That's right!
Wait, there's two YouTubers! Yeah, there's a YouTuber here!
What? I don't know how long it's been edited.
I know, right? Why did you pick them?
You want to try it? No big reason. We just thought we'd give it a try.
We're doing the editing too. We're working on it.
But Maika's good at that.
I started at the same time as Maika, but she's been teaching me.
What? That's so cool! One of these days... when we're on the bullet train...
Hold on, I'm cutting.
I'll do it.
Maybe they'll update it.
Soon! I'm so glad! We'll do it again.
Meat!
Meat! Meat check!
We're open! Is it bad?
Are you sure? It's good!
Fire! Wiener is on fire!
Wait! Come on! Come on!
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Should we move?
It smells so good.
Ready?
Are the vegetables ready? What do you think?
I think it's good!
Hooyah!
Wiener?
That's good!
Yeah! Visual!
Okay?
What have you been doing the last few days?
Sleeping!
I slept 14 hours today.
Isn't 14 hours great?
That's basically more than half.
That's great.
There's not a lot of running around on stage at night.
That's right.
We sit on the floor and stuff.
But there's a lot of dialogue.
So you have to keep your head on a swivel.
So it's a very brain-intensive performance.
Yes, it was.
So when I got home, I was already passed out.
That's right.
How do you remember your lines?
I want to hear it.
I want to hear it. I really want to hear it.
This gal's play...
I thought, "If a person can do it, they can do it.
I mean, there were so many lines.Because there were so many lines.
There were long lines and stuff.
Sometimes I'd learn the basics in the bathtub.
That's right.
It's hard to remember when you're talking to each other.
So you go to the rehearsal hall and look at the script
I'll look at the script and think, "Oh, I've memorized it.
I see.
It's a practice.
Yeah.
That's awesome.
You should eat it.
You want some?
Eat it. Eat your hatta kaltin.
Bon appétit.
Look at the seasoning.
I'll just leave it as it is.
How do you like it?
Good reaction.
Is it good?
Bibi!
Bibi, you got it.
It's really good.
Bon appétit!
A little spicy
Delicious!
Grass?
The grass on top adds flavor.
It adds flavor.
What a winner!
Looks delicious!
It's delicious, isn't it?
Wait, that looks good.
Isn't this a nice sight?
You want to film it? Here.
You want me to put it up?
Yeah, let's do it.
That's great.
Can we get someone to do it?
Not us.
That's not you!
That's not us!
Every time... we'll do it to say goodbye to someone.
Let's do it!
Let's give the Rosemuse a good night's sleep.
Is that okay? Okay.
That was pretty fast-paced.
Yeah, it was.
I'm working on a new one a month.
It's a lot of work, but it's fun.
It's really amazing.
You know, there are only a few people in this world who can do what they love.
There are only a few people in this world who can do what they love.
That's why I really think I have a good job.
I'm so grateful and happy.
There are a lot of things that bother me, but...
But in the end, it's what I want to do.
Then tell me about your dreams for the future.
You tell me.
You're going to tell me, aren't you? Like this.
Dreams.
As a loop, to be honest...
I'm pretty sure I dropped it.
A pure white dress.
It's a white dress, but it's covered in olive oil.
Why are you wearing this?
Sorry.
Hey, why are you wearing a white dress?
So, what were we talking about?
I was trying to have a nice talk.
Someone spilled it.
I just want everyone to be happy.
That's the best I can do.
I know it's irresponsible.
I just want them to be happy.
I really do.
Because, of course, on a big stageBecause, of course, I want to be on a big stage.
I want to go to a bigger stage.
I want to see more scenery with everyone, but...
But if someone could go, but they weren't happy...
What's the point?
That's why I want everyone to be happy.
Of course I want to go on a big stage.
But... you know... everyone seemed to be having fun.
You can tell, can't you?
You can feel the atmosphere between the members.
When the overchairs were on...
This is how it's going to be.
You could see it.
You know, the lights.
We're behind the LEDs.
I can already see the view.
A beautiful view.
Oh, my God! That was great.
Everyone make eye contact.
Each and every one of you looked so happy.
Seeing their happy faces made me happy, too.
I have a great memory of how happy I was when I saw their happy faces.
The making of the DVD of the live concert.
I rewound it so many times.
I'm embarrassed to say it, but...
I'm embarrassed to say it, but at the end when we leave the stage, only the members are there.
They all get together there and slap each other's backs so much.
Everybody's hugging each other.
At the end, we all say how cute we are.
And then we do it one more time.
It was so good, I loved it.
Is this also done inside?
On April 29th.
We'll be in our 7th year.
That's great!
Seven years.
That's great.
It'll be fun to have all the members.
What?
Kihara's 19 now?
He'll be 19 next time.
One more year?
A little over a year?
I bet Kihara would have fun.
It would be fun.
It'll be unique.
I'm going to get rid of my usual frustrations.
Kihara's definitely up for it.
I want to see it so bad.
I'll definitely do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sure it'll be great.
When I joined the group, I couldn't even drink with everyone else.
And even when I turned 20 and started drinking...
You didn't drink much, right?
That's right.
When did you start drinking like this?
Wasn't it pretty big when you drank with the others?
That was a big one.
We'll talk about it.
You didn't have dinner with them?
No.
We didn't really talk about anything deep.
If it was before...
So you called her... and said, "Hey, you guys are coming to my place tomorrow, right?
No, they won't. They'll be there.
I'll be there.
I'd love to do this on a regular basis.
I'd like to do this on a regular basis.
Please watch and comment a lot!
I'm sure we'll be able to add more and more projects as we go along.
Please do!
I don't know why I said "please" with a bright red star.
But, well, it's been three years.
When the cameras stop rolling, you can drink as much as you want.
Let's drink till morning.
Let's drink.
So, bye-bye.